getdriver.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy - GetDriver

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

We have chosen to show only non-personalized ads to users in the EEA. You may also want to read their guide to Opt out of seeing personalized ads at the following URL <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en-GB>.

**Social Media Sharing**  
In addition to G+ button we also have [Addthis](http://www.addthis.com/) sharing buttons on our site to help make it easier to share our content on those platforms. You can see the G+ privacy policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy) and Addthis Privacy Policy [here](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/). You can opt out here (Addthis): <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out/>

**Google Analytics  
**This is used to track website usage in aggregate. We do not use it to track individual users. Settings we are currently using: Remarketing: OFF, Advertising Reporting Features: OFF, User and event data retention: Set to expire after 14 months (shortest option), Reset on new activity: ON, User-ID: OFF. Accepted GDPR Data Processing Amendment. Google currently offers an Analytics [opt-out here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en).

**Facebook Like Box (Page Plugin)**  
If a user clicks the “Like” button then they will be redirected to Facebook.com and prompted to log into their account, if they are not already. Facebook.com will then add some temporary cookies to their browser in order to keep them logged in. These cookies can be deleted via your web browser privacy settings. Deleting the cookies will log you out of Facebook.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting GetDriver.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. You can opt out here: <http://statcounter.com/about/set-refusal-cookie/>

**Links to Third Party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy then you may contact us at  
[  
https://www.getdriver.com/contact](https://www.getdriver.com/contact)

Software & Drivers Downloads for Windows 10, Windows 8.1, Windows 8, Windows 7, Vista & XP
